question_data = [
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia is the irrational fear of long words.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                       "question": "The Pythagorean theorem states that the square of the hypotenuse "
                                                   "is equal to the product of the squares of the other two sides.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies "
                 "Interstellar and The Martian.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "There are no roads in or out of Juneau, Alaska.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "San Marino is the only country completely surrounded by another "
                                                   "country.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Kill La Kill, the weapon of the main protagonist is a katana. ", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Despite being seperated into multiple countries, The Scandinavian "
                                                  "countries are unified by all having the same monarch.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A flock of crows is known as a homicide.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Switzerland has four national languages, English being one of them.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;Rich Uncle Pennybags&quot; from the board game &quot;Monopoly&quot; wears a monocle.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
